>> Brian Holt: 因此，让我们快速转换 app.js ，但我们不希望这样做。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So let's go convert app.js
really quick, cuz we don't want this to
是， >> Brian Holt: 我们只是希望它是 JSX。
be,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Just we want it to be JSX.
所以我要说回来
So I'm gonna say return.
我们先讲一下括号，为什么我把括号放在这里呢 ?
Let's talk about the parentheses for just
a second, why do I put parentheses here?
如果我只说回话然后再做点新的事
Well, if I just say return and
then put something on a new line, and
我把它放在一条新线上，让它更容易阅读。
I put it on a new line so
it's easier to read.
那么 JavaScript 的工作方式是如果它看到一条新的线
Well, the way the JavaScript
works is if it sees a new line,
就在这里结束
it just ends it right here.
所以它实际上是这样运作的，就在那里，对吧 ?
So it actually works like that,
where it just ends, right?
所以如果我把这个包围在括号里
So if I surround this in parenthesis,
it's saying hey,
我还没结束呢继续下去
I'm not done yet,
continue on to the next line.
>> Brian Holt: 好，因此 h1>采用
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and so h1&gt;Adopt
我就像这样
Me!, like that.
现在我想用我在这里做的宠物组件对吧
And then now I wanna use this Pet
component that I made up here, right?
那我要怎么用这个
So how am I gonna use that?
这就像这样佩特
Well, it works like this, Pet.
所以我实际上可以用一个合成组件，就像它是真实的 HTML，
So I actually can use a composite
component as if it was real HTML,
这很酷
which is really cool.
如果我想在这里加上那个 ID 的话
And then if I wanted to
add that ID back here, so
这个 ID 是，我叫它重要的，对，就像这样。
this ID would be, I called it
something important, right, like that.
此方法的工作方式与属性或属性相同
That works the same way, and
attributes or properties for
这个宠物组件的工作方式是一样的所以我可以说名字叫 " Luna"
this pet component works exactly the same
way, so I can say name = "Luna",
>> Brian Holt: Animal = "Bird"或 no，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Animal = "Bird", or no,
" 犬" ，并繁殖 " Havanese"。
"Dog", and breed = "Havanese".
>> Brian Holt: 现在，你看到了这个自我封闭的标签，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now, you see this
self-closing tag thing, right?
我知道 HTML 是很有选择性的而且我经常把它放外面
I know in HTML that that's optional and
frequently I leave it out, cuz again,
我很懒也不喜欢那种东西
I'm lazy and don't type things like that.
但我要告诉你，在 JSX 中，他们是必需的，对吗 ?
But I'll tell you that in JSX they
actually are required, right?
您需要让 JSX 知道这是一个自动关闭的标记，因此
You need to let JSX know that
this is a self-closing tag so
你得把它放在后面
you have to put that trailing slash.
好吧我要放三个
Okay, I'm gonna put three of those.
这就是 " 百事可乐 "
This was "Pepper",
" 鸟人 "" 鸡尾酒 "
"Bird", "Cockatiel", and
这就是 " Doink" 混合 "Cat"
this was "Doink", mixed "Cat".
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: What is kinda fun though,
还有 JX 你甚至可以做自我关闭的潜水夫
with JSX you can even do self-closing
divs as well, like that.
这在 HTML 中是不合法的，但在 JSX 中是合法的，这很有趣。
Which is not legal in HTML but
is legal in JSX, which is kinda fun.
> > Brian Holt: 实际上， Prettier 会为您做。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And actually,
Prettier will just do it for you.
如果我这样做，当我拯救的时候，就像是，不，你真的是说，这挺有趣的。
If I do that, when I save, it's like, no,
you really meant that, which is kinda fun.
>> 扬声器 2: 因此 JSX 将执行此操作并将其转换为 React.create，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So JSX would take this and
turn it into a React.create,
第一个自变量是 div，第二个是 emptyObject，
with the first argument being div,
the second one being emptyObject,
第三个是 React.nett 的列表
and the third one being a list of
React.creates with all of those?
>> Brian Holt: 对。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yep.
>> 演讲者 2: 因此写作的好处是什么
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So
what's the benefit of writing
XML 将其转换为 JavaScript，以将其转换为 HTML?
XML to turn it into JavaScript,
to turn it into HTML?
>> Brian Holt: 对。 >> 扬声器 2: 为什么不只是
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yep.
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Why don't it just
写 HTML?
write HTML?
>> Brian Holt: 最终，这是某种类型的模板，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Ultimately,
this is a template of some sort, right?
有点错误的对吧
Kind of falsely so, right?
它不是一个模板，实际上只是函数调用。
Cuz it's not actually a template,
it's actually just function calls.
但是在最后，这其实是势在必行的，
But in the end,
this is actually imperative,
因为它被处死了对吧
cuz it's being executed, right?
虽然 HTML 是声明式的，但它不是您可以执行的内容，对吗 ?
Whereas HTML is declarative,
it's not something you can execute, right?
那么到目前为止我所展示的一切，都是非常静态的数据，对吗 ?
So everything I've shown you so far,
this is all very static data, right?
但你可以想象到这里而不是像 Luna 一样
But you can imagine here,
instead of having Luna equal this,
我可能有 API 结果对吧
I could have API result, right?
现在我可以把动态信息传递给宠物
And now I can pass dynamic
information into Pet.
它让我有能力操纵这个
It gives me the power of
JavaScript to manipulate this.
这能回答你的问题吗
Does that answer your question?
>> 演讲者 2: 是的，谢谢。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, thank you.
>> Brian Holt: Cool， yep.
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Cool, yep.
>> Brian Holt: 实际上，沿着这些线，我觉得我跳过了
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So actually, along those
lines, I think something that I skipped
解释是这里的花括号
over explaining were the curly
braces over here, and
让我们尽快解决这个问题
let's address that really quickly.
所以现在如果我过去看看我的网站
So right now, if I go over and
look at my site,
我觉得一切都要修复了，等等，还有一件事要解决。
I think everything should be fixed again,
hold on, one more thing to fix here.
与其在此处创建 React.create 链接，请使此应用程序成为类似的应用程序。
Rather than having a React.create link
down here, make this app like that.
> > Brian Holt: 再次，第 31 行，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So again, line 31 there,
只要让React.打造一个这样的应用
just make that React.create
an App like that.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 好吧，既然我已经这样做了，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
now that I've done that,
回到 Pet.js
go back over to Pet.js.
如果我去我的应用程序，希望它还在运行。
And if I go over to my app,
hopefully it's still running.
不不是那个那个
No, not that one, this one.
我阻止它跑了吗
Did I stop it from running?
我做了， npm 跑了。
I did, npm run dev.
>> Brian Holt: 刷新页面。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Refresh the page.
我有 Luna， Pepper和 Doink，对吧 ?
So I have Luna, Pepper, and Doink, right?
如果我在这儿把花括号去掉怎么办
What happens if I remove
the curly braces here?
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 现在真的是名字了，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now it's literally
gonna be the name, right?
所以如果我救了这个
So if I save this and
回到这里你会看到上面写着名字的对吧
go back over here you'll see that it says
literally the word name here, right?
那么花括号的是你让 JSX 知道这事
So what the curly braces do is
you're letting JSX know this is
此处是 JavaScript 表达式。
a JavaScript expression in here.
而术语表达式意味着任何可以在
And the term expression means anything
that can be on the right side of
任务。
an assignment.
所以如果我说 const x = 什么
So if I say const x = something,
让我们说吧 >> Brian Holt: 我
let's just say,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I
不知道， named.toUpperCase}，对吧 ?
don't know, named.toUpperCase}, right?
任何可以在等号右边出现的东西
So anything that can be on the right
side of an equals sign here,
这被认为是一种表达方式。
this is considered an expression.
>> Brian Holt: 例如，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So for example,
你不能在右边有一个声明对吧
you can't have an if statement
on the right side of it, right?
所以 const y = if，
So a const y = if,
这不起作用，因为一个表达式和一个语句是不同的，对吗 ?
this doesn't work because an expression
and a statement are different, right?
一个说法是完整的，对吧 ?
A statement is a whole idea, right?
因此所有第 3 行都将被视为一个语句，但是
So all of line three would be
considered one statement, but
这里的一切都被认为是一种表达方式
everything here on the right side
is considered an expression.
这种界定是否有意义 ?
Does that delineation make sense?
好的，所以在这里，我可以说， . toUpperCase ，并引用该权限
Okay, so that means here inside of name, I
can say .toUpperCase and invoke that right
在这里，或者这可能是在援引动物，功能之类的，或者
here, or this could be invoking animal,
the function, or something like that, or
这个可以是 + 动物，对吧 ?
this can be + animal, right?
所以任何东西都能在一个等号的右边
So anything that can be on the right
side of an equal sign, but
我不能在里面放一个完整的声明
I can't put a full if statement in there.
但是你可以用长长的，对吧 ?
But you can use ternaries, right?
可爱的长长的胸骨在技术上是表达的
Cuz ternaries are technically expressions,
and
一个三元的问题就像问号的问题。
a ternary is like the question mark thing.
我待会儿用
I'll use them later.
他们很有趣或者不好玩，取决于你问谁。
They're fun or not fun,
depending on who you ask.
我觉得他们很有趣
I think they're fun.
所以反正现在我都搞砸了，对，所以
So anyway, and again, yeah,
now I've messed up everything, right, so
现在卢娜都是大写的你有 HavaneseDog 和 CockatielBird，对吧 ?
now Luna is all capitalized, and you have
HavaneseDog and CockatielBird, right?
>> Brian Holt: 这就是这些内容的内容。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
that's what those are about.
它只是一个卷曲的大支柱，就是这样运作的。
And it's just a single curly brace there,
that's how it works.
>> Brian Holt: 这样你就可以
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And so you can mix and
我也可以有这样的名字
match them too, so
I could have name like that.
如果我回到这里，它的名字叫 Luna，名字叫 Pepper ，
And if I go back here,
it says Name: Luna, Name: Pepper, and
都是为了你的
it does that concatenation for you.